# Cristiane Lehmkuhl



linkedin.com/in/crisleh



crisleh@gmail.com



+61 478 793 023

# Summary

Education and professional experience in the fields of fashion design, business, and sales. Having that combined with formal training in project management, I have delivered several projects in the fashion and eyewear industries. As a retail store manager in Sunglass Hut, I have consistently beaten my target KPIs and KCIs, along with building a winning retail sales team.

Australian Permanent Resident with full working rights.

# **Experience**



# **Retail Manager**

#### Sunglass Hut

Jun 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

As the store manager of one of the Sunglass Hut busiest shops in QVB, I have assembled a team that has consistently achieved the goals set by the organisation. My mission is to deliver excellent customer service, motivate the sales team to meet their objectives, hiring and training new staff, manage their rooster and drive sales every day.



#### Student

#### TAFE NSW

Oct 2016 - Mar 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Enrolled in the AMEP and SELPT Retail programs, where besides taking general english lessons, I learned about migrating and living in Australia, obtained professional qualifications to work in retail and finished by undertaking an internship in Woolworths.

#### **Career Break**

#### Sabbatical

Apr 2014 - Mar 2016 (2 years)

Moved to Europe, where I decided to take a career break to focus on family and my wellbeing. During this time, I engaged in small casual jobs, enrolled in German lessons and traveled a lot.



# **Project Manager**

#### JR Adamver

Jun 2012 - Jan 2014 (1 year 8 months)

Coordination of projects and product innovation for the largest brands in the Brazilian eyewear industry, such as Absurda, Colcci, Forum and Mormaii. Responsibilities included market analysis, visual merchandising, marketing material, sales coordination, retail training, e-learning courses coordination and after-sales services.



## Product Analyst

#### **Audaces**

Feb 2009 - Jun 2012 (3 years 5 months)

As a product analyst of the leading group in technological solutions for the fashion industry in Latin America, I developed several activities in market analysis, product innovation, customer support, sales and training. Having product expertise, I helped to drive sales across South America and Europe on multiple occasions.

#### падисня Intern

Naguchi

Oct 2007 - Sep 2008 (1 year)

Internship in the area of process, control and plan in the textile industry. Acquired valuable experience in product technical specifications, technical drawing and management of the production line.

### Education

#### FURB - Universidade de Blumenau

Bachelor's degree, Fashion/Apparel Design 2004 - 2009



### FURB - Universidade de Blumenau

Postgraduate, Business in the Fashion Industry 2008 - 2010



### Senac Santa Catarina

Graduate, Project Management

2012 - 2013

Based on the principles of all areas of PMBOK.



# 📕 VEC - Valor e Competência

Graduate, Project Management

2012 - 2013

Specialisation using case methods and dynamics driven by the topics of the PMBOK®, PRINCE2™, agile management, soft skills and so on.

# **Skills**

Project Management • Retail Sales • Team Leadership • Sales • Visual Merchandising • Agile Project Management • Recruiting • Manufacturing • Employee Training • Instructor-led Training